{
  "title": "Decimals Operations",
  "description": "Work with decimals like a pro! Whether it's shopping, measuring, or solving tricky problems, practice decimal operations in a game that rewards accuracy and speed!",
  "waves": 5,
  "timePerQuestion": 30,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $8.0 - 0.6$?",
      "choices": [
        "$7.4$",
        "$7.9$",
        "$7.2$",
        "$6.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.4$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $9.7 + 5.5$?",
      "choices": [
        "$15.0$",
        "$15.2$",
        "$15.4$",
        "$15.6$"
      ],
      "answer": "$15.2$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $4.7 - 2.3$?",
      "choices": [
        "$2.8$",
        "$2.4$",
        "$2.5$",
        "$1.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.4$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $9.2 + 4.5$?",
      "choices": [
        "$13.6$",
        "$13.7$",
        "$14.0$",
        "$13.3$"
      ],
      "answer": "$13.7$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $0.7 + 3.0$?",
      "choices": [
        "$3.5$",
        "$3.9$",
        "$4.2$",
        "$3.7$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.7$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $7.5 + 2.7$?",
      "choices": [
        "$10.5$",
        "$10.6$",
        "$10.1$",
        "$10.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$10.2$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $9.6 - 6.3$?",
      "choices": [
        "$3.2$",
        "$3.7$",
        "$3.6$",
        "$3.3$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.3$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $7.8 + 1.7$?",
      "choices": [
        "$9.7$",
        "$9.1$",
        "$9.5$",
        "$9.4$"
      ],
      "answer": "$9.5$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $8.3 - 0.3$?",
      "choices": [
        "$8.4$",
        "$8.0$",
        "$8.5$",
        "$7.7$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.0$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $5.0 + 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$5.6$",
        "$5.1$",
        "$5.0$",
        "$5.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.1$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $3.1 - 1.0$?",
      "choices": [
        "$2.1$",
        "$1.7$",
        "$2.5$",
        "$2.4$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.1$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $7.4 + 1.8$?",
      "choices": [
        "$9.0$",
        "$8.7$",
        "$9.2$",
        "$8.8$"
      ],
      "answer": "$9.2$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $8.2 - 3.5$?",
      "choices": [
        "$4.4$",
        "$4.7$",
        "$4.5$",
        "$4.8$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.7$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $7.0 - 5.4$?",
      "choices": [
        "$1.4$",
        "$1.6$",
        "$2.0$",
        "$1.1$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.6$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $9.0 + 6.7$?",
      "choices": [
        "$15.7$",
        "$15.8$",
        "$16.0$",
        "$15.5$"
      ],
      "answer": "$15.7$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $0.2 + 9.7$?",
      "choices": [
        "$10.0$",
        "$9.9$",
        "$9.7$",
        "$9.5$"
      ],
      "answer": "$9.9$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $8.2 - 1.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$7.5$",
        "$7.1$",
        "$6.6$",
        "$7.4$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.1$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $4.2 + 9.0$?",
      "choices": [
        "$12.8$",
        "$13.2$",
        "$13.3$",
        "$13.1$"
      ],
      "answer": "$13.2$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $8.2 - 8.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.1$",
        "$-0.2$",
        "$-0.3$",
        "$0.6$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.1$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $1.6 + 3.5$?",
      "choices": [
        "$5.1$",
        "$5.0$",
        "$5.5$",
        "$5.6$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.1$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $8.5 - 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$8.0$",
        "$8.4$",
        "$8.2$",
        "$8.3$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.4$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $1.7 - 1.5$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.0$",
        "$0.1$",
        "$0.3$",
        "$0.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.2$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $1.1 + 3.6$?",
      "choices": [
        "$4.6$",
        "$4.7$",
        "$4.9$",
        "$5.0$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.7$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $5.9 - 4.4$?",
      "choices": [
        "$1.8$",
        "$1.5$",
        "$1.3$",
        "$1.0$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.5$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $7.8 - 6.8$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.7$",
        "$1.3$",
        "$1.0$",
        "$1.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.0$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $3.8 - 1.5$?",
      "choices": [
        "$2.8$",
        "$2.3$",
        "$2.4$",
        "$2.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.3$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $2.9 + 4.0$?",
      "choices": [
        "$6.9$",
        "$7.3$",
        "$7.4$",
        "$6.4$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.9$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $8.3 - 7.0$?",
      "choices": [
        "$1.2$",
        "$1.3$",
        "$1.5$",
        "$0.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.3$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $3.4 + 6.0$?",
      "choices": [
        "$9.3$",
        "$9.4$",
        "$9.0$",
        "$8.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$9.4$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $7.4 + 6.6$?",
      "choices": [
        "$14.0$",
        "$13.7$",
        "$14.1$",
        "$14.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$14.0$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $6.4 + 9.5$?",
      "choices": [
        "$15.4$",
        "$15.9$",
        "$15.7$",
        "$16.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$15.9$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $7.6 - 5.8$?",
      "choices": [
        "$1.7$",
        "$1.3$",
        "$1.8$",
        "$2.3$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.8$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $2.4 - 0.5$?",
      "choices": [
        "$1.8$",
        "$1.9$",
        "$1.7$",
        "$2.3$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.9$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $2.6 + 7.8$?",
      "choices": [
        "$10.8$",
        "$10.5$",
        "$10.4$",
        "$10.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$10.4$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $5.7 - 0.2$?",
      "choices": [
        "$5.5$",
        "$5.4$",
        "$5.9$",
        "$5.1$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.5$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $6.5 + 6.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$12.9$",
        "$12.4$",
        "$12.1$",
        "$12.6$"
      ],
      "answer": "$12.6$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $2.9 + 7.7$?",
      "choices": [
        "$10.5$",
        "$11.0$",
        "$10.6$",
        "$10.8$"
      ],
      "answer": "$10.6$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $0.3 + 6.5$?",
      "choices": [
        "$6.7$",
        "$7.3$",
        "$6.8$",
        "$7.0$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.8$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $7.2 - 3.7$?",
      "choices": [
        "$3.5$",
        "$3.9$",
        "$3.3$",
        "$3.0$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.5$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $3.8 - 2.0$?",
      "choices": [
        "$2.0$",
        "$1.8$",
        "$1.7$",
        "$1.4$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.8$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $8.5 + 8.7$?",
      "choices": [
        "$17.4$",
        "$17.2$",
        "$17.3$",
        "$17.6$"
      ],
      "answer": "$17.2$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $9.0 - 5.4$?",
      "choices": [
        "$3.7$",
        "$3.6$",
        "$3.9$",
        "$3.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.6$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $4.3 + 0.9$?",
      "choices": [
        "$5.2$",
        "$4.8$",
        "$5.1$",
        "$5.0$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.2$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $7.9 - 2.7$?",
      "choices": [
        "$4.8$",
        "$5.4$",
        "$4.9$",
        "$5.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.2$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $5.2 + 6.6$?",
      "choices": [
        "$11.9$",
        "$11.8$",
        "$12.1$",
        "$11.5$"
      ],
      "answer": "$11.8$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $8.7 + 5.3$?",
      "choices": [
        "$14.4$",
        "$14.3$",
        "$14.0$",
        "$14.1$"
      ],
      "answer": "$14.0$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $0.3 + 7.8$?",
      "choices": [
        "$7.6$",
        "$8.1$",
        "$8.4$",
        "$7.8$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.1$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $9.5 + 8.9$?",
      "choices": [
        "$18.2$",
        "$18.1$",
        "$18.4$",
        "$18.6$"
      ],
      "answer": "$18.4$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $0.8 + 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$1.3$",
        "$0.6$",
        "$1.0$",
        "$0.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.9$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "wave": 1,
      "question": "What is $7.5 + 3.5$?",
      "choices": [
        "$10.8$",
        "$11.3$",
        "$11.0$",
        "$10.7$"
      ],
      "answer": "$11.0$",
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $3.4 \\times 6$.",
      "choices": [
        "$19.4$",
        "$20.4$",
        "$20.6$",
        "$21.4$"
      ],
      "answer": "$20.4$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $45.91 \\times 0.01$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.459$",
        "$0.454$",
        "$0.458$",
        "$0.455$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.459$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $94.8 \\times 0.01$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.952$",
        "$0.943$",
        "$0.948$",
        "$0.945$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.948$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $1.9 \\times 3$.",
      "choices": [
        "$5.67$",
        "$5.71$",
        "$5.72$",
        "$5.7$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.7$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $3.6 \\times 3$.",
      "choices": [
        "$10.3$",
        "$10.8$",
        "$11.1$",
        "$10.5$"
      ],
      "answer": "$10.8$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $83.06 \\times 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$8.303$",
        "$8.306$",
        "$8.305$",
        "$8.301$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.306$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $1.24 \\times 7$.",
      "choices": [
        "$8.69$",
        "$8.67$",
        "$8.66$",
        "$8.68$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.68$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $2.2 \\times 4$.",
      "choices": [
        "$8.8$",
        "$9.3$",
        "$8.7$",
        "$9.1$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.8$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $1.8 \\times 7$.",
      "choices": [
        "$12.1$",
        "$12.7$",
        "$12.5$",
        "$12.6$"
      ],
      "answer": "$12.6$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $4.52 \\times 8$.",
      "choices": [
        "$36.22$",
        "$36.04$",
        "$36.16$",
        "$36.31$"
      ],
      "answer": "$36.16$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $0.22 \\times 8$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.75$",
        "$1.78$",
        "$1.74$",
        "$1.76$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.76$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $10.38 + 2.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$12.43$",
        "$12.48$",
        "$12.49$",
        "$12.47$"
      ],
      "answer": "$12.48$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $98.0 \\times 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$9.805$",
        "$9.796$",
        "$9.797$",
        "$9.8$"
      ],
      "answer": "$9.8$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $82.4 \\times 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$8.235$",
        "$8.243$",
        "$8.24$",
        "$8.241$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.24$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $31.77 \\times 0.01$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.317$",
        "$0.319$",
        "$0.318$",
        "$0.313$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.318$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $95.88 \\times 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$9.59$",
        "$9.591$",
        "$9.584$",
        "$9.588$"
      ],
      "answer": "$9.588$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $5.2 - 1.28$?",
      "choices": [
        "$3.9$",
        "$4.2$",
        "$4.1$",
        "$4.4$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.9$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $82.99 \\times 0.01$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.832$",
        "$0.83$",
        "$0.828$",
        "$0.829$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.83$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $2.49 \\times 4$.",
      "choices": [
        "$10.0$",
        "$9.98$",
        "$9.93$",
        "$9.96$"
      ],
      "answer": "$9.96$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $41.75 \\times 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$4.18$",
        "$4.179$",
        "$4.174$",
        "$4.175$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.175$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $81.87 \\times 0.01$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.824$",
        "$0.819$",
        "$0.815$",
        "$0.814$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.819$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $47.2 \\times 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$4.723$",
        "$4.719$",
        "$4.72$",
        "$4.716$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.72$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $11.88 - 7.95$?",
      "choices": [
        "$3.93$",
        "$3.98$",
        "$3.92$",
        "$3.88$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.93$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $7.38 - 5.62$?",
      "choices": [
        "$1.77$",
        "$1.71$",
        "$1.76$",
        "$1.78$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.76$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $3.62 + 3.67$?",
      "choices": [
        "$7.28$",
        "$7.29$",
        "$7.3$",
        "$7.33$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.29$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $76.1 \\times 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$7.61$",
        "$7.614$",
        "$7.608$",
        "$7.615$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.61$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $2.8 \\times 3$.",
      "choices": [
        "$8.4$",
        "$8.3$",
        "$8.7$",
        "$8.0$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.4$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $13.69 - 0.22$?",
      "choices": [
        "$13.43$",
        "$13.47$",
        "$13.44$",
        "$13.46$"
      ],
      "answer": "$13.47$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $37.6 \\times 0.01$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.376$",
        "$0.375$",
        "$0.371$",
        "$0.377$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.376$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $23.7 \\times 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$2.371$",
        "$2.375$",
        "$2.37$",
        "$2.368$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.37$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $3.0 \\times 9$.",
      "choices": [
        "$27.4$",
        "$26.6$",
        "$27.0$",
        "$26.4$"
      ],
      "answer": "$27.0$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $13.69 - 7.89$?",
      "choices": [
        "$5.79$",
        "$5.8$",
        "$5.81$",
        "$5.83$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.8$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $10.2 - 4.3$?",
      "choices": [
        "$6.0$",
        "$5.6$",
        "$5.7$",
        "$5.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.9$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $56.33 \\times 0.01$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.564$",
        "$0.567$",
        "$0.566$",
        "$0.563$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.563$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $1.08 \\times 2$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.16$",
        "$2.21$",
        "$2.14$",
        "$2.17$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.16$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $4.14 - 0.48$?",
      "choices": [
        "$3.63$",
        "$3.7$",
        "$3.65$",
        "$3.66$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.66$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $6.7 - 4.7$?",
      "choices": [
        "$2.0$",
        "$1.7$",
        "$1.9$",
        "$2.5$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.0$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $3.8 \\times 7$.",
      "choices": [
        "$27.6$",
        "$25.6$",
        "$26.6$",
        "$26.8$"
      ],
      "answer": "$26.6$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $5.9 + 1.8$?",
      "choices": [
        "$7.8$",
        "$7.7$",
        "$7.2$",
        "$7.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.7$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "Calculate $2.31 \\times 3$.",
      "choices": [
        "$6.91$",
        "$6.92$",
        "$6.93$",
        "$6.89$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.93$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $63.6 \\times 0.01$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.631$",
        "$0.636$",
        "$0.637$",
        "$0.64$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.636$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $17.2 \\times 0.01$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.167$",
        "$0.169$",
        "$0.172$",
        "$0.171$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.172$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $3.44 + 9.9$?",
      "choices": [
        "$13.33$",
        "$13.34$",
        "$13.3$",
        "$13.35$"
      ],
      "answer": "$13.34$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $6.5 - 5.0$?",
      "choices": [
        "$1.3$",
        "$1.5$",
        "$2.0$",
        "$1.2$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.5$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $5.9 + 1.96$?",
      "choices": [
        "$7.8$",
        "$8.0$",
        "$7.9$",
        "$8.1$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.9$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $7.08 + 1.45$?",
      "choices": [
        "$8.51$",
        "$8.52$",
        "$8.53$",
        "$8.5$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.53$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $8.15 + 9.8$?",
      "choices": [
        "$17.98$",
        "$17.95$",
        "$18.0$",
        "$17.97$"
      ],
      "answer": "$17.95$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $19.4 \\times 0.01$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.194$",
        "$0.195$",
        "$0.198$",
        "$0.199$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.194$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $88.0 \\times 0.1$?",
      "choices": [
        "$8.795$",
        "$8.799$",
        "$8.796$",
        "$8.8$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.8$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "wave": 2,
      "question": "What is $13.4 + 0.4$?",
      "choices": [
        "$14.0$",
        "$13.8$",
        "$13.7$",
        "$13.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$13.8$",
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 101,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $41.0 \\div 4$.",
      "choices": [
        "$10.254$",
        "$10.245$",
        "$10.251$",
        "$10.25$"
      ],
      "answer": "$10.25$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 102,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(1.0 - 0.2) \\times 0.4$.",
      "choices": [
        "$0.27$",
        "$0.29$",
        "$0.32$",
        "$0.34$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.32$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 103,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $2.36 \\times 0.17$.",
      "choices": [
        "$0.398$",
        "$0.404$",
        "$0.397$",
        "$0.401$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.401$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 104,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $49.5 \\div 9$.",
      "choices": [
        "$5.49$",
        "$5.47$",
        "$5.54$",
        "$5.5$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.5$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 105,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $43.75 \\div 7$.",
      "choices": [
        "$6.26$",
        "$6.21$",
        "$6.25$",
        "$6.24$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.25$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 106,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $22.5 \\div 5$.",
      "choices": [
        "$4.52$",
        "$4.55$",
        "$4.5$",
        "$4.51$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.5$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 107,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $1.38 \\times 2.0$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.759$",
        "$2.764$",
        "$2.76$",
        "$2.758$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.76$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 108,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(1.23 - 0.4) \\div 0.5$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.67$",
        "$1.7$",
        "$1.66$",
        "$1.63$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.66$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 109,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $4.3 \\times 3.93$.",
      "choices": [
        "$16.87$",
        "$16.9$",
        "$16.86$",
        "$16.92$"
      ],
      "answer": "$16.9$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 110,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(3.78 - 0.2) \\div 1.9$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.88$",
        "$1.83$",
        "$1.93$",
        "$1.87$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.88$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 111,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $16.0 \\div 4$.",
      "choices": [
        "$4.0$",
        "$3.97$",
        "$4.05$",
        "$4.01$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.0$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 112,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $35.0 \\div 5$.",
      "choices": [
        "$7.05$",
        "$6.98$",
        "$6.99$",
        "$7.0$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.0$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 113,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(1.78 + 1.5) \\div 1.1$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.96$",
        "$2.95$",
        "$2.98$",
        "$3.03$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.98$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 114,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(0.22 + 1.7) \\div 1.0$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.92$",
        "$1.93$",
        "$1.96$",
        "$1.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.92$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 115,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $26.0 \\div 8$.",
      "choices": [
        "$3.25$",
        "$3.24$",
        "$3.23$",
        "$3.27$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.25$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 116,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(2.77 - 0.8) \\div 0.8$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.49$",
        "$2.47$",
        "$2.51$",
        "$2.46$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.46$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 117,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $0.1 \\times 5.0$.",
      "choices": [
        "$0.504$",
        "$0.499$",
        "$0.505$",
        "$0.5$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.5$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 118,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $2.55 \\times 1.13$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.91$",
        "$2.87$",
        "$2.88$",
        "$2.85$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.88$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 119,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(2.69 + 1.0) \\div 1.0$.",
      "choices": [
        "$3.65$",
        "$3.66$",
        "$3.72$",
        "$3.69$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.69$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 120,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(0.8 - 0.5) \\times 1.6$.",
      "choices": [
        "$0.49$",
        "$0.5$",
        "$0.51$",
        "$0.48$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.48$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 121,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(4.4 + 2.7) \\times 0.8$.",
      "choices": [
        "$5.68$",
        "$5.73$",
        "$5.7$",
        "$5.67$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.68$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 122,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(1.8 - 0.7) \\times 1.3$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.4$",
        "$1.38$",
        "$1.43$",
        "$1.48$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.43$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 123,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(2.8 - 2.0) \\times 1.9$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.49$",
        "$1.54$",
        "$1.52$",
        "$1.56$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.52$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 124,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(3.2 + 0.6) \\times 1.7$.",
      "choices": [
        "$6.46$",
        "$6.48$",
        "$6.41$",
        "$6.49$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.46$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 125,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $24.5 \\div 7$.",
      "choices": [
        "$3.54$",
        "$3.45$",
        "$3.5$",
        "$3.48$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.5$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 126,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(4.66 + 2.8) \\div 1.2$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.52$",
        "$1.53$",
        "$1.54$",
        "$1.55$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.55$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 127,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $3.7 \\times 4.42$.",
      "choices": [
        "$16.357$",
        "$16.354$",
        "$16.358$",
        "$16.349$"
      ],
      "answer": "$16.354$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 128,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $11.0 \\div 2$.",
      "choices": [
        "$5.497$",
        "$5.504$",
        "$5.496$",
        "$5.5$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.5$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 129,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(2.39 - 0.2) \\div 0.7$.",
      "choices": [
        "$3.16$",
        "$3.09$",
        "$3.14$",
        "$3.13$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.13$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 130,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(1.1 + 2.9) \\times 1.5$.",
      "choices": [
        "$5.98$",
        "$6.0$",
        "$5.99$",
        "$6.04$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.0$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 131,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $42.0 \\div 4$.",
      "choices": [
        "$10.5$",
        "$10.503$",
        "$10.496$",
        "$10.504$"
      ],
      "answer": "$10.5$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 132,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $4.52 \\times 1.2$.",
      "choices": [
        "$5.4$",
        "$5.45$",
        "$5.42$",
        "$5.39$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.42$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 133,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $28.0 \\div 7$.",
      "choices": [
        "$3.99$",
        "$4.03$",
        "$4.02$",
        "$4.0$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.0$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 134,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $0.28 \\times 1.58$.",
      "choices": [
        "$0.44$",
        "$0.47$",
        "$0.43$",
        "$0.46$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.44$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 135,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $1.2 \\times 2.06$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.472$",
        "$2.475$",
        "$2.468$",
        "$2.471$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.472$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 136,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $1.95 \\times 2.9$.",
      "choices": [
        "$5.6553$",
        "$5.655$",
        "$5.6555$",
        "$5.6546$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.655$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 137,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(4.9 - 2.4) \\times 0.6$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.48$",
        "$1.5$",
        "$1.51$",
        "$1.49$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.5$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 138,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $36.0 \\div 6$.",
      "choices": [
        "$5.99$",
        "$5.95$",
        "$5.97$",
        "$6.0$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.0$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 139,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $1.53 \\times 0.5$.",
      "choices": [
        "$0.765$",
        "$0.7651$",
        "$0.7645$",
        "$0.7648$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.765$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 140,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(2.3 - 0.8) \\times 1.7$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.56$",
        "$2.57$",
        "$2.59$",
        "$2.55$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.55$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 141,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Divide $28.5 \\div 2$.",
      "choices": [
        "$14.253$",
        "$14.252$",
        "$14.248$",
        "$14.25$"
      ],
      "answer": "$14.25$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 142,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(4.7 + 0.5) \\times 1.5$.",
      "choices": [
        "$7.75$",
        "$7.8$",
        "$7.76$",
        "$7.83$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.8$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 143,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $4.4 \\times 3.42$.",
      "choices": [
        "$15.05$",
        "$15.0$",
        "$15.04$",
        "$15.1$"
      ],
      "answer": "$15.05$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 145,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $3.59 \\times 2.55$.",
      "choices": [
        "$9.154$",
        "$9.156$",
        "$9.15$",
        "$9.155$"
      ],
      "answer": "$9.154$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 146,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(3.9 - 1.3) \\times 1.9$.",
      "choices": [
        "$4.94$",
        "$4.9$",
        "$4.95$",
        "$4.92$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.94$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 147,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(2.8 + 2.2) \\times 0.3$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.53$",
        "$1.45$",
        "$1.5$",
        "$1.55$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.5$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 148,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Multiply $0.41 \\times 2.7$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.13$",
        "$1.12$",
        "$1.11$",
        "$1.14$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.11$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 149,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(3.4 - 1.1) \\times 0.8$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.89$",
        "$1.8$",
        "$1.84$",
        "$1.88$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.84$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 150,
      "wave": 3,
      "question": "Calculate $(3.0 - 0.2) \\div 0.2$.",
      "choices": [
        "$13.97$",
        "$14.04$",
        "$13.98$",
        "$14.0$"
      ],
      "answer": "$14.0$",
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 151,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Divide $4.65$ by $0.5$.",
      "choices": [
        "$9.3$",
        "$9.2997$",
        "$9.2998$",
        "$9.3005$"
      ],
      "answer": "$9.3$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 152,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $6.91$. If you buy $3$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$20.73$",
        "$20.75$",
        "$20.63$",
        "$20.67$"
      ],
      "answer": "$20.73$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 153,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $9.01$. If you buy $7$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$63.31$",
        "$63.07$",
        "$62.77$",
        "$62.83$"
      ],
      "answer": "$63.07$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 154,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Divide $7.22$ by $4.676$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.5438$",
        "$1.544$",
        "$1.5443$",
        "$1.5441$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.5441$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 155,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $8.13$ and $2.486$.",
      "choices": [
        "$20.213$",
        "$20.211$",
        "$20.207$",
        "$20.219$"
      ],
      "answer": "$20.211$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 156,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $4.22 + (1.14 \\div 2.06)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$4.773$",
        "$4.771$",
        "$4.769$",
        "$4.775$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.773$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 157,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $2.67$. If you buy $6$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$15.98$",
        "$16.0$",
        "$16.02$",
        "$16.04$"
      ],
      "answer": "$16.02$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 158,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $10.28 - (2.71 \\div 0.42)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$3.829$",
        "$3.828$",
        "$3.823$",
        "$3.826$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.828$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 159,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Divide $5.1$ by $1.811$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.8162$",
        "$2.8165$",
        "$2.8161$",
        "$2.8157$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.8161$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 160,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $8.03 - (0.42 \\div 2.54)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$7.86$",
        "$7.868$",
        "$7.865$",
        "$7.863$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.865$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 161,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $6.77$ and $3.499$.",
      "choices": [
        "$23.688$",
        "$23.6882$",
        "$23.689$",
        "$23.6892$"
      ],
      "answer": "$23.6882$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 162,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $12.39$. If you buy $7$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$86.65$",
        "$86.73$",
        "$86.97$",
        "$87.13$"
      ],
      "answer": "$86.73$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 163,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $9.99 - (2.05 \\div 1.29)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$8.402$",
        "$8.401$",
        "$8.399$",
        "$8.403$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.401$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 164,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $3.19$. If you buy $3$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$9.58$",
        "$9.57$",
        "$9.55$",
        "$9.53$"
      ],
      "answer": "$9.57$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 165,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Divide $3.704$ by $1.388$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.6691$",
        "$2.6686$",
        "$2.6681$",
        "$2.6685$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.6686$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 166,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $2.84 - (1.94 \\div 1.09)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.057$",
        "$1.06$",
        "$1.058$",
        "$1.059$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.06$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 167,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $9.875$ and $0.79$.",
      "choices": [
        "$7.804$",
        "$7.801$",
        "$7.8$",
        "$7.806$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.801$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 168,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $9.05 - (0.88 \\div 1.24)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$8.335$",
        "$8.339$",
        "$8.34$",
        "$8.336$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.34$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 169,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $8.75$. If you buy $6$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$52.5$",
        "$52.7$",
        "$52.25$",
        "$52.35$"
      ],
      "answer": "$52.5$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 170,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $9.36 + (1.75 \\times 1.77)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$12.453$",
        "$12.455$",
        "$12.456$",
        "$12.457$"
      ],
      "answer": "$12.457$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 171,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $7.63 + (2.6 \\times 0.93)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$10.047$",
        "$10.048$",
        "$10.049$",
        "$10.053$"
      ],
      "answer": "$10.048$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 172,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $5.19 - (4.19 \\times 2.49)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.432$",
        "$2.437$",
        "$2.441$",
        "$2.439$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.437$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 173,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $9.61$. If you buy $10$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$96.55$",
        "$96.1$",
        "$96.28$",
        "$95.92$"
      ],
      "answer": "$96.1$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 174,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $9.59$. If you buy $2$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$19.23$",
        "$19.18$",
        "$19.15$",
        "$19.19$"
      ],
      "answer": "$19.18$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 175,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $9.715$ and $3.33$.",
      "choices": [
        "$32.3509$",
        "$32.35$",
        "$32.3494$",
        "$32.3503$"
      ],
      "answer": "$32.3509$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 176,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Divide $4.6$ by $4.032$.",
      "choices": [
        "$1.1411$",
        "$1.141$",
        "$1.1408$",
        "$1.1409$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.1409$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 177,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $4.95$ and $3.975$.",
      "choices": [
        "$19.6763$",
        "$19.6762$",
        "$19.6764$",
        "$19.6759$"
      ],
      "answer": "$19.6762$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 178,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $1.26$ and $4.02$.",
      "choices": [
        "$5.065$",
        "$5.068$",
        "$5.07$",
        "$5.067$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.065$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 179,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $3.51 - (1.43 \\div 1.2)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.315$",
        "$2.317$",
        "$2.318$",
        "$2.322$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.318$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 180,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $10.53$. If you buy $8$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$84.48$",
        "$84.24$",
        "$84.16$",
        "$84.4$"
      ],
      "answer": "$84.24$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 181,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Divide $5.9$ by $0.71$.",
      "choices": [
        "$8.3099$",
        "$8.3096$",
        "$8.3094$",
        "$8.3104$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.3099$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 182,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $13.5$. If you buy $5$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$67.32$",
        "$67.5$",
        "$67.38$",
        "$67.56$"
      ],
      "answer": "$67.5$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 183,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $4.5$ and $4.96$.",
      "choices": [
        "$22.32$",
        "$22.3192$",
        "$22.3208$",
        "$22.3202$"
      ],
      "answer": "$22.32$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 184,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $14.29$. If you buy $9$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$128.61$",
        "$129.09$",
        "$128.37$",
        "$129.21$"
      ],
      "answer": "$128.61$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 185,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $5.26$. If you buy $9$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$47.5$",
        "$47.54$",
        "$47.38$",
        "$47.34$"
      ],
      "answer": "$47.34$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 186,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $1.68$. If you buy $10$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$16.8$",
        "$16.85$",
        "$16.75$",
        "$16.84$"
      ],
      "answer": "$16.8$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 187,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $2.16$. If you buy $3$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$6.47$",
        "$6.43$",
        "$6.5$",
        "$6.48$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.48$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 188,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $6.24 - (1.47 \\div 0.52)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$3.415$",
        "$3.414$",
        "$3.416$",
        "$3.413$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.413$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 189,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $9.28$. If you buy $3$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$27.84$",
        "$27.74$",
        "$27.78$",
        "$27.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$27.84$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 190,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $7.855$ and $1.44$.",
      "choices": [
        "$11.3117$",
        "$11.3111$",
        "$11.3112$",
        "$11.3108$"
      ],
      "answer": "$11.3112$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 191,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $7.85$ and $3.78$.",
      "choices": [
        "$29.6734$",
        "$29.6728$",
        "$29.672$",
        "$29.673$"
      ],
      "answer": "$29.673$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 192,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $9.15$. If you buy $8$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$73.48$",
        "$73.2$",
        "$73.06$",
        "$72.85$"
      ],
      "answer": "$73.2$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 193,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $1.81$. If you buy $2$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$3.62$",
        "$3.65$",
        "$3.66$",
        "$3.64$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.62$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 194,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $3.532$ and $4.01$.",
      "choices": [
        "$14.162$",
        "$14.165$",
        "$14.163$",
        "$14.167$"
      ],
      "answer": "$14.163$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 195,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $3.74 - (2.0 \\div 2.2)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.835$",
        "$2.826$",
        "$2.831$",
        "$2.834$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.831$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 196,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $10.69$. If you buy $8$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$85.52$",
        "$85.36$",
        "$85.2$",
        "$85.12$"
      ],
      "answer": "$85.52$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 197,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Divide $8.63$ by $4.12$.",
      "choices": [
        "$2.093$",
        "$2.095$",
        "$2.091$",
        "$2.096$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.095$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 198,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Find the product of $2.671$ and $0.13$.",
      "choices": [
        "$0.348$",
        "$0.351$",
        "$0.347$",
        "$0.349$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.347$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 199,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "An item costs $5.88$. If you buy $6$ of them, what is the total cost?",
      "choices": [
        "$35.34$",
        "$35.22$",
        "$35.31$",
        "$35.28$"
      ],
      "answer": "$35.28$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 200,
      "wave": 4,
      "question": "Calculate $6.14 + (0.72 \\div 2.11)$.",
      "choices": [
        "$6.478$",
        "$6.483$",
        "$6.485$",
        "$6.481$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.481$",
      "points": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 201,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $166.7$. He spent $7.19$ on groceries and $29.24$ on books. Then he earned $9.19$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$139.2$",
        "$139.85$",
        "$139.46$",
        "$139.07$"
      ],
      "answer": "$139.46$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 202,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $88.14$. He spent $13.84$ on groceries and $17.84$ on books. Then he earned $3.49$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$59.95$",
        "$60.15$",
        "$59.8$",
        "$59.9$"
      ],
      "answer": "$59.95$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 203,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $3.55 - \\frac{3}{8}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$3.176$",
        "$3.177$",
        "$3.175$",
        "$3.178$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.175$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 204,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(12.54 + 8.95) \\times 0.82 \\div 1.47$.",
      "choices": [
        "$11.9873$",
        "$11.9879$",
        "$11.9872$",
        "$11.9876$"
      ],
      "answer": "$11.9876$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 205,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(13.3 + 4.72) \\times 1.04 \\div 1.24$.",
      "choices": [
        "$15.113$",
        "$15.1136$",
        "$15.1135$",
        "$15.1134$"
      ],
      "answer": "$15.1135$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 206,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $134.12$. He spent $9.27$ on groceries and $19.54$ on books. Then he earned $4.06$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$109.77$",
        "$109.37$",
        "$109.57$",
        "$108.87$"
      ],
      "answer": "$109.37$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 207,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $60.84$. He spent $6.3$ on groceries and $29.71$ on books. Then he earned $6.29$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$31.18$",
        "$31.12$",
        "$31.0$",
        "$31.21$"
      ],
      "answer": "$31.12$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 208,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $\\frac{3}{10} + 1.2$?",
      "choices": [
        "$1.495$",
        "$1.5$",
        "$1.505$",
        "$1.499$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.5$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 209,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(17.04 + 3.53) \\times 2.85 \\div 0.17$.",
      "choices": [
        "$344.8432$",
        "$344.85$",
        "$344.8636$",
        "$344.8602$"
      ],
      "answer": "$344.85$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 210,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $5.18 - \\frac{7}{8}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$4.309$",
        "$4.305$",
        "$4.301$",
        "$4.303$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.305$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 211,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(19.24 + 9.08) \\times 4.58 \\div 0.58$.",
      "choices": [
        "$223.6325$",
        "$223.6303$",
        "$223.6259$",
        "$223.6215$"
      ],
      "answer": "$223.6303$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 212,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $70.73$. He spent $15.49$ on groceries and $15.42$ on books. Then he earned $3.65$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$43.47$",
        "$43.31$",
        "$43.43$",
        "$43.51$"
      ],
      "answer": "$43.47$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 213,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $89.13$. He spent $19.37$ on groceries and $13.15$ on books. Then he earned $2.93$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$59.59$",
        "$59.54$",
        "$59.44$",
        "$59.49$"
      ],
      "answer": "$59.54$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 214,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $7.8 - \\frac{3}{10}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$7.504$",
        "$7.501$",
        "$7.502$",
        "$7.5$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.5$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 215,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $1.4 - \\frac{1}{8}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$1.27$",
        "$1.275$",
        "$1.271$",
        "$1.277$"
      ],
      "answer": "$1.275$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 216,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(6.42 + 6.5) \\times 4.32 \\div 1.33$.",
      "choices": [
        "$41.9657$",
        "$41.9641$",
        "$41.9669$",
        "$41.9637$"
      ],
      "answer": "$41.9657$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 217,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(6.32 + 4.16) \\times 1.36 \\div 1.08$.",
      "choices": [
        "$13.197$",
        "$13.1967$",
        "$13.1966$",
        "$13.1968$"
      ],
      "answer": "$13.197$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 218,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $7.04 - \\frac{2}{5}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$6.641$",
        "$6.64$",
        "$6.638$",
        "$6.642$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.64$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 219,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $184.66$. He spent $13.84$ on groceries and $23.12$ on books. Then he earned $7.97$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$155.82$",
        "$155.37$",
        "$155.67$",
        "$156.27$"
      ],
      "answer": "$155.67$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 220,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $194.65$. He spent $16.14$ on groceries and $10.88$ on books. Then he earned $2.11$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$170.38$",
        "$169.42$",
        "$169.1$",
        "$169.74$"
      ],
      "answer": "$169.74$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 221,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(13.38 + 8.72) \\times 3.96 \\div 1.82$.",
      "choices": [
        "$48.0845$",
        "$48.0837$",
        "$48.0857$",
        "$48.0873$"
      ],
      "answer": "$48.0857$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 222,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $184.09$. He spent $16.62$ on groceries and $25.83$ on books. Then he earned $4.56$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$146.2$",
        "$145.5$",
        "$145.92$",
        "$145.78$"
      ],
      "answer": "$146.2$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 223,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $159.65$. He spent $8.23$ on groceries and $27.71$ on books. Then he earned $4.46$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$128.41$",
        "$128.53$",
        "$127.57$",
        "$128.17$"
      ],
      "answer": "$128.17$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 224,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $73.45$. He spent $5.67$ on groceries and $11.14$ on books. Then he earned $2.89$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$59.53$",
        "$59.33$",
        "$59.73$",
        "$59.68$"
      ],
      "answer": "$59.53$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 225,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(9.69 + 4.69) \\times 4.02 \\div 0.87$.",
      "choices": [
        "$66.4455$",
        "$66.4443$",
        "$66.4437$",
        "$66.4431$"
      ],
      "answer": "$66.4455$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 226,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $\\frac{1}{2} + 6.2$?",
      "choices": [
        "$6.7$",
        "$6.697$",
        "$6.698$",
        "$6.695$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.7$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 227,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $137.61$. He spent $8.37$ on groceries and $22.77$ on books. Then he earned $7.37$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$113.84$",
        "$114.17$",
        "$113.62$",
        "$114.28$"
      ],
      "answer": "$113.84$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 228,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $74.96$. He spent $16.29$ on groceries and $28.66$ on books. Then he earned $5.42$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$35.43$",
        "$35.31$",
        "$35.28$",
        "$35.49$"
      ],
      "answer": "$35.43$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 229,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $166.08$. He spent $10.39$ on groceries and $12.16$ on books. Then he earned $4.25$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$147.08$",
        "$147.92$",
        "$147.78$",
        "$147.36$"
      ],
      "answer": "$147.78$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 230,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $8.89 - \\frac{1}{4}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$8.645$",
        "$8.636$",
        "$8.638$",
        "$8.64$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.64$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 231,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(16.04 + 2.31) \\times 0.65 \\div 0.95$.",
      "choices": [
        "$12.555$",
        "$12.5553$",
        "$12.5556$",
        "$12.5558$"
      ],
      "answer": "$12.5553$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 232,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $5.93 - \\frac{3}{8}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$5.56$",
        "$5.555$",
        "$5.55$",
        "$5.557$"
      ],
      "answer": "$5.555$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 233,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(12.31 + 8.16) \\times 0.68 \\div 0.14$.",
      "choices": [
        "$99.4257$",
        "$99.4248$",
        "$99.4293$",
        "$99.4275$"
      ],
      "answer": "$99.4257$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 234,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $141.03$. He spent $15.07$ on groceries and $11.35$ on books. Then he earned $8.35$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$122.48$",
        "$122.84$",
        "$123.2$",
        "$122.96$"
      ],
      "answer": "$122.96$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 235,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $\\frac{1}{8} + 6.22$?",
      "choices": [
        "$6.349$",
        "$6.347$",
        "$6.345$",
        "$6.348$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.345$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 236,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(15.84 + 1.84) \\times 1.76 \\div 0.97$.",
      "choices": [
        "$32.078$",
        "$32.0792$",
        "$32.0801$",
        "$32.0789$"
      ],
      "answer": "$32.0792$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 237,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $184.08$. He spent $18.33$ on groceries and $17.57$ on books. Then he earned $2.33$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$151.26$",
        "$150.51$",
        "$150.96$",
        "$150.06$"
      ],
      "answer": "$150.51$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 238,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $174.06$. He spent $19.25$ on groceries and $27.88$ on books. Then he earned $7.91$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$134.32$",
        "$134.71$",
        "$135.36$",
        "$134.84$"
      ],
      "answer": "$134.84$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 239,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $3.56 - \\frac{7}{10}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$2.861$",
        "$2.86$",
        "$2.859$",
        "$2.856$"
      ],
      "answer": "$2.86$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 240,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(15.38 + 2.98) \\times 3.31 \\div 0.68$.",
      "choices": [
        "$89.3716$",
        "$89.3668$",
        "$89.366$",
        "$89.37$"
      ],
      "answer": "$89.37$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 241,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $\\frac{7}{8} + 5.57$?",
      "choices": [
        "$6.442$",
        "$6.445$",
        "$6.45$",
        "$6.449$"
      ],
      "answer": "$6.445$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 242,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $\\frac{4}{5} + 9.77$?",
      "choices": [
        "$10.574$",
        "$10.572$",
        "$10.568$",
        "$10.57$"
      ],
      "answer": "$10.57$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 243,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $9.2 - \\frac{4}{5}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$8.4$",
        "$8.397$",
        "$8.395$",
        "$8.405$"
      ],
      "answer": "$8.4$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 244,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $\\frac{1}{2} + 4.0$?",
      "choices": [
        "$4.5$",
        "$4.498$",
        "$4.504$",
        "$4.502$"
      ],
      "answer": "$4.5$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 245,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $1.0 - \\frac{5}{8}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$0.37$",
        "$0.378$",
        "$0.375$",
        "$0.377$"
      ],
      "answer": "$0.375$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 246,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $84.73$. He spent $12.07$ on groceries and $21.05$ on books. Then he earned $7.27$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$59.03$",
        "$58.63$",
        "$58.88$",
        "$58.78$"
      ],
      "answer": "$58.88$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 247,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "Evaluate $(10.23 + 7.55) \\times 0.76 \\div 1.92$.",
      "choices": [
        "$7.0384$",
        "$7.0374$",
        "$7.0375$",
        "$7.0379$"
      ],
      "answer": "$7.0379$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 248,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "What is $4.48 - \\frac{7}{8}$?",
      "choices": [
        "$3.605$",
        "$3.609$",
        "$3.6$",
        "$3.601$"
      ],
      "answer": "$3.605$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 249,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $101.7$. He spent $8.15$ on groceries and $21.35$ on books. Then he earned $6.22$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$78.42$",
        "$78.63$",
        "$78.49$",
        "$78.56$"
      ],
      "answer": "$78.42$",
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 250,
      "wave": 5,
      "question": "John started with $118.83$. He spent $11.24$ on groceries and $26.0$ on books. Then he earned $6.85$ from a small task. How much money does John have now?",
      "choices": [
        "$88.44$",
        "$88.76$",
        "$88.2$",
        "$88.84$"
      ],
      "answer": "$88.44$",
      "points": 30
    }
  ]
}